Miller, Aubrey L., Chairman Collection of A. T. & S. F. Railway General Grievance Committee Records 6321
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Chairman Aubrey L. Miller Collection of A. T. & S. F. Railway General Grievance Committee Records
1924-1987
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Miller, Aubrey L.
Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen (BLF&E)
Atchison, Topeka and Santa Fe Railway (AT&SF)
United Transportation Union (UTU)
6321
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
7289386
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, June 28, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6321 MB: Chairman Aubrey L. Miller Collection of A. T. & S. F. Railway General Grievance Committee Memorabilia 6321 P: Chairman Aubrey L. Miller Collection of A. T. & S. F. Railway General Grievance Committee Photographs
Collective labor agreements--Railroads; Miller, Aubrey L.; Atchison, Topeka, and Santa Fe Railway Company; Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen; United Transportation Union
7289386
- Election of Board of Trustees, A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, 1924-1927 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- On-Duty Injuries, Operating Crafts, 1961-1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents
  Cases
- On-Duty Injuries, Operating Crafts, 1959-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Correspondence
- On-Duty Injuries, Non-Operating Crafts, 1960-1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- On-Duty Injuries, Non-Operating Crafts, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- On-Duty Injuries, Non-Operating Crafts, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- On-Duty Injuries, Non-Operating Crafts, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Board of Trustees Proposed Reorganization, 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Board of Trustees Reorganization, 1945-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Board of Trustees Amending Charter and Revising Bylaws, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Claims, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Claims, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Claims, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association, Charter, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Resolution of RLEA, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- United Transportation Union (UTU) [folder 1 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Court transcript: Case 80C1573
- United Transportation Union (UTU) [folder 2 of 2], 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- United Transportation Union (UTU), 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Court transcript: Case CIV 81-685 HB
- A. L. Miller Personal, 1944-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- News Clippings, 1951-1987 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- A. T. & S. F. Employes' Benefit Association Bylaws, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- A. T. & S. F. Hospital Association Instructions, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)